

DAVI NAIZER

Front-end Web Developer

PROFILE

I have been creating web and learning content for almost 18 years now. I have worked on many projects throughout these years along leading companies like Kraft Foods, Electrolux, Volvo Motors, HSBC Bank, Furukawa Electric, GP Strategies, Metlife, Boticário Group and many others.

As a tech enthusiast and an eager learner, I'm always looking for new tools and ways to improve mine and team's quality of life.

CONTACT



+55 41 99206-1260



davi.naizer@gmail.com



Curitiba/PR, Brazil



linkedin.com/in/davi-naizer



davi.naizer



davinaizer.github.io/myportfolio

SKILLS

HARD-SKILLS

- · AS3, JS, HTML, CSS, SQL, OOP, UML
- \cdot jQuery, BackboneJS, ReactJS
- · SVN, GIT
- · Linux, LAMP, AWS EC2
- · Trello, Toggl, Microsoft Project

SOFT-SKILLS

- Flexibility
- Communication
- · Teamworking
- · Attention to Detail
- · Self-Starter Attitude
- Analytical and Problem Solver
- · Quality-oriented

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017-Pesent

FREELANCE FRONT-END DEVELOPER

2009-2017

CO-FOUNDER & DEVELOPMENT MANAGER

UNBOX Learning Experience

Relevant Achievements:

- · Managed for more than 7 years a small (about 12 people), but successful e-learning, tech, and design company.
- Decreased in ~65% the time taken to develop an online course/e-learning from ~3 months to ~4 weeks. This was achieved by developing an e-learning framework (see E-book Framework in my portfolio) and implementing tools for team, time and tasks management. As well a workflow and changes in all production stages: briefing, conception, UX/UI design, development, product deliver and quality control.

As a Manager:

- · Planning, delegation and communication;
- · Digital learning solutions conception;
- · Research & propose new products;
- · Strategic Planning;
- · Writing Proposals for Business;
- · Coach and Mentoring.

As a Developer:

Develop and implement:

- · Customized e-Learning solutions (AS3, HTML, CSS, JS);
- · Game-based learning (AS3, OOP);
- \cdot Learning Management Systems LMS (Moodle, HTML, JS, CSS, AWS EC2, Linux).

As a Partner/Director:

- · Pricina:
- · Organize and track financial information;
- · Financial reports review.

2007-2009

LEAD WEB DEVELOPER

G/PAC Comunicação Integrada

As a Team Lead:

 \cdot Responsible for planning, delegation, communication, and time management.

As a Developer:

- Translate instructional concepts into interactive graphics or animations:
- · E-Learning development (Flash, AS, SCORM);
- · Game-based learning development (Flash, AS3, OOP, SCORM);
- · Promotional Websites development (HTML, CSS, JS).

2005-2007

E-LEARNING DEVELOPER

HSBC Bank Brasil

- · Develop, test and implement tools for learning content authoring (ASP, SQL Server)
- · Learning Management System administration (LMS)
- · Server administration (Windows Server)

2001-2005

WEB/ACTIONSCRIPT DEVELOPER

G/PAC Comunicação Integrada

Develop, test and implement:

- · Web-based applications (HTML, JS, ASP, SQLServer)
- $\cdot\,$ Online Courses (Flash, AS, SCORM)
- · Game-based learning (Flash, AS)
- · Multimedia presentations (Flash, AS)



EDUCATION

•	2007-2010	COMPUTER ENGINEERING
		POSITIVO UNIVERSITY, CURITIBA/PARANÁ
•	2005-2006	ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING POSITIVO UNIVERSITY, CURITIBA/PARANÁ
•	1997-2000	ELECTRONICS
		FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY - PARANÁ (UTFPR)